<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Site</title>
    <link>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://sergeantgarik.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>My Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/media/icon_hu7729264130191091259.png</url>
      <title>My Site</title>
      <link>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Example Talk</title>
      <link>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/event/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2030 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/event/example/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;flex px-4 py-3 mb-6 rounded-md bg-primary-100 dark:bg-primary-900&#34;&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;pr-3 pt-1 text-primary-600 dark:text-primary-300&#34;&gt;
  &lt;svg height=&#34;24&#34; xmlns=&#34;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 24 24&#34;&gt;&lt;path fill=&#34;none&#34; stroke=&#34;currentColor&#34; stroke-linecap=&#34;round&#34; stroke-linejoin=&#34;round&#34; stroke-width=&#34;1.5&#34; d=&#34;m11.25 11.25l.041-.02a.75.75 0 0 1 1.063.852l-.708 2.836a.75.75 0 0 0 1.063.853l.041-.021M21 12a9 9 0 1 1-18 0a9 9 0 0 1 18 0m-9-3.75h.008v.008H12z&#34;/&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&#34;dark:text-neutral-300&#34;&gt;Click on the &lt;strong&gt;Slides&lt;/strong&gt; button above to view the built-in slides feature.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slides can be added in a few ways:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create&lt;/strong&gt; slides using Hugo Blox Builder&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.hugoblox.com/reference/content-types/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Slides&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; feature and link using &lt;code&gt;slides&lt;/code&gt; parameter in the front matter of the talk file&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Upload&lt;/strong&gt; an existing slide deck to &lt;code&gt;static/&lt;/code&gt; and link using &lt;code&gt;url_slides&lt;/code&gt; parameter in the front matter of the talk file&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Embed&lt;/strong&gt; your slides (e.g. Google Slides) or presentation video on this page using &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.hugoblox.com/reference/markdown/&#34;&gt;shortcodes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Further event details, including &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.hugoblox.com/reference/markdown/&#34;&gt;page elements&lt;/a&gt; such as image galleries, can be added to the body of this page.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/experience/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Post from September 25 to October 1</title>
      <link>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/post/summary4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/post/summary4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-happened-this-week&#34;&gt;What Happened This Week&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2509&#34;&gt;25.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today we covered complex topics in differential equations during the lecture. Realized that I need more practice. Decided to change my workplace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2709&#34;&gt;27.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Started working at a new coffee shop! The atmosphere here is incredible, and the customers are very friendly. Even had an interesting conversation with a mathematician!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2809&#34;&gt;28.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gathered with my group to prepare for the upcoming test. Everyone shared their knowledge and methods. The evening at work was busy, but I managed well!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2909&#34;&gt;29.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Had a Knowledge Festival at the faculty today! Participated in various contests and quizzes. After work, met some old friends — it was great to reminisce about school days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;3009&#34;&gt;30.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Faced some challenges with my studies today — couldn&amp;rsquo;t solve a few problems. Asked my classmates for help, and they were happy to assist. Work was also tough, but I got through it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;0110&#34;&gt;01.10&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reflecting on the month: studied hard, worked, and met some great people. I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m growing and developing! Hoping the next month will be just as eventful!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Post from September 18 to 24</title>
      <link>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/post/summary3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/post/summary3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-happened-this-week&#34;&gt;What Happened This Week&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2009&#34;&gt;20.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Took a break from studying and went to the gym. Physical activity helps me unwind. In the evening, worked, and my colleagues joined in a conversation about sports!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2209&#34;&gt;22.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Met with my Mathematical Analysis professor for a consultation. He suggested some useful resources. After work at the café, we talked about his favorite books!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2309&#34;&gt;23.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Got together with my group to work on a project. Discussed interesting problems. In the evening, there was a rush of customers at work, which only added to the adrenaline!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2409&#34;&gt;24.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today is a day off! Finally took a break from studying and working. Went to a museum exhibition, got inspired by new ideas. Back to the grind tomorrow!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence in the Modern World</title>
      <link>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/publication/ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/publication/ai/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Artificial Intelligence (AI) has become an integral part of our daily lives and is transforming various sectors. From healthcare technologies to financial services, AI is being implemented across numerous industries, enhancing efficiency and service quality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In healthcare, AI assists in diagnosing diseases by analyzing medical images and patient data with high accuracy. This enables doctors to make more informed decisions and reduces diagnostic time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In business, AI optimizes processes by analyzing large volumes of data to identify trends and predict consumer behavior. Chatbots and virtual assistants improve customer service by providing round-the-clock support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, the rise of AI also brings challenges. Ethical issues related to data privacy and the potential replacement of human labor require attention. Society must find a balance between innovation and responsible technology use.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Post from September 11 to 17</title>
      <link>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/post/summary2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/post/summary2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-happened-this-week&#34;&gt;What Happened This Week&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1609&#34;&gt;16.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today was the first quiz on Linear Algebra. I was a bit nervous, but I think I did okay. In the evening, back at work, but thoughts about the quiz keep lingering!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1709&#34;&gt;17.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spent the whole day at the library. So many books! Found some useful materials for preparing for the next quiz. Work at the café was calm, and I even managed to read a bit.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Machines and Their Benefits for IT</title>
      <link>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/publication/vm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/publication/vm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Virtual machines (VMs) have become an integral part of the modern information world, providing numerous benefits for developers, system administrators, and companies as a whole. They are software emulations of physical computers, allowing multiple operating systems to run on a single physical server. Let&amp;rsquo;s look at the main advantages of virtual machines and their impact on the IT field.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resource Savings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the main advantages of virtual machines is the saving of hardware resources. Instead of using separate physical servers for each task, organizations can run multiple VMs on a single server. This reduces costs for equipment, electricity, and cooling, as well as simplifies infrastructure management.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexibility and Scalability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Virtual machines provide high flexibility in resource management. If needed, a new VM can be quickly created or the configuration of an existing one can be changed. This is especially useful for companies experiencing fluctuating loads or planning growth. Scaling infrastructure becomes easier and faster, allowing for quick responses to changes in the business.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;3&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Security and Isolation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each virtual machine operates in its own isolated environment, which increases security. If one VM is attacked or fails, the others remain unaffected. This allows for testing new applications or systems without risk to the main infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;4&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Simplified Testing and Development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Virtual machines are ideal for software testing. Developers can quickly create and delete test environments, speeding up the development process and allowing experiments without risking the main system. This significantly reduces the time to market for a product.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;5&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Easier Backup and Recovery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Virtual machines simplify the processes of data backup and recovery. System administrators can create snapshots of VM states, allowing for quick restoration of the system to a previous state in case of failure or error.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Benefits of Individual Projects in Education</title>
      <link>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/publication/proj/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/publication/proj/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Individual projects are becoming increasingly popular in educational institutions, and this is no coincidence. They represent a powerful tool that promotes a deeper understanding of material and the development of key skills in students.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development of Independence and Responsibility&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Working on an individual project requires students to plan independently, organize their time, and complete tasks. This fosters the development of responsibility for their own learning and outcomes, which is an important skill in future life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-Depth Study of a Topic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Individual projects allow students to choose topics that genuinely interest them. This makes the learning process more engaging and motivating. An in-depth study of a specific topic helps to better understand the material and apply it in practice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;3&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development of Critical Thinking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Project work requires analyzing information, evaluating various sources, and drawing one&amp;rsquo;s own conclusions. This fosters the development of critical thinking, a necessary skill in the modern world where information is abundantly available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;4&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative Approach to Learning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Individual projects open up space for creativity. Students can use various methods and formats to present their ideas—ranging from scientific papers to multimedia presentations. This helps develop creativity and find unconventional solutions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;5&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preparation for Real-World Challenges&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Individual projects often simulate real situations that students may encounter in their future professional activities. This provides an opportunity to develop skills such as research, data analysis, and result presentation, which will be valuable in their careers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent Breakthroughs in Mathematics</title>
      <link>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/publication/math/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/publication/math/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In recent years, mathematics continues to amaze with new discoveries and breakthroughs that open new horizons in various scientific fields. One significant achievement has been the resolution of the Birch and Swinnerton-Dyer hypothesis, concerning the properties of elliptic curves. This discovery, made by a group of researchers, may have profound implications for number theory and cryptography.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another important event has been the development of machine learning theory, where mathematicians apply complex algorithms to analyze large datasets. The application of optimization methods and linear algebra allows for significant improvements in prediction quality in fields such as medicine and finance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also noteworthy are the achievements in topology, where researchers study the properties of spaces that remain unchanged under continuous deformations. Breakthroughs in this area help to better understand the structure of multidimensional objects and have applications in physics and computer science.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These achievements highlight the importance of mathematics as a foundation for many scientific disciplines and demonstrate that even more exciting discoveries lie ahead. Mathematics continues to be a driving force for progress in our world.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Post from September 1 to 3</title>
      <link>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/post/summary1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/post/summary1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-happened-this-week&#34;&gt;What Happened This Week&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;0109&#34;&gt;01.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today was my first day at the university! So many new faces and impressions. I was a bit nervous during the Mathematical Analysis lecture, but the professor turned out to be very friendly. In the evening, I worked at the café and met some interesting people!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;0309&#34;&gt;03.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, my classmates and I decided to meet for coffee after classes. We discussed the upcoming exams and shared our study methods. I worked until late in the evening, but it didn’t stop me from feeling positive!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Day First Day at the Capital University</title>
      <link>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/publication/1sept/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/publication/1sept/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The first day of September is not just the start of autumn, but also the long-awaited Knowledge Day. For many students, this day symbolizes new opportunities and discoveries. At the capital university, the atmosphere was particularly exciting: the halls were filled with the laughter and conversation of first-year students who were eagerly awaiting the start of the academic year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the morning, senior students greeted the new students at the university entrance with smiles and good wishes. The hosts conducted a ceremonial line-up where congratulations and motivational words from the faculty were shared. Every new student felt like part of a large and friendly family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the official part, introductions with teachers and classmates began. The lectures in mathematics and literature opened doors to the world of knowledge that lay ahead. Despite the nervousness, many first-year students noted how quickly they found common ground with each other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the evening, after a busy day, students gathered at a café, discussing their impressions and plans for the future. Knowledge Day became not only the beginning of the academic year but also the start of a new chapter in each of their lives. With hope and optimism, they looked forward, ready for new challenges and achievements.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
