<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog | My Site</title>
    <link>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/post/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://sergeantgarik.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/media/icon_hu7729264130191091259.png</url>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/post/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Post from September 25 to October 1</title>
      <link>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/post/summary4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/post/summary4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-happened-this-week&#34;&gt;What Happened This Week&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2509&#34;&gt;25.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today we covered complex topics in differential equations during the lecture. Realized that I need more practice. Decided to change my workplace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2709&#34;&gt;27.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Started working at a new coffee shop! The atmosphere here is incredible, and the customers are very friendly. Even had an interesting conversation with a mathematician!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2809&#34;&gt;28.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gathered with my group to prepare for the upcoming test. Everyone shared their knowledge and methods. The evening at work was busy, but I managed well!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2909&#34;&gt;29.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Had a Knowledge Festival at the faculty today! Participated in various contests and quizzes. After work, met some old friends — it was great to reminisce about school days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;3009&#34;&gt;30.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Faced some challenges with my studies today — couldn&amp;rsquo;t solve a few problems. Asked my classmates for help, and they were happy to assist. Work was also tough, but I got through it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;0110&#34;&gt;01.10&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reflecting on the month: studied hard, worked, and met some great people. I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m growing and developing! Hoping the next month will be just as eventful!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Post from September 18 to 24</title>
      <link>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/post/summary3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/post/summary3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-happened-this-week&#34;&gt;What Happened This Week&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2009&#34;&gt;20.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Took a break from studying and went to the gym. Physical activity helps me unwind. In the evening, worked, and my colleagues joined in a conversation about sports!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2209&#34;&gt;22.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Met with my Mathematical Analysis professor for a consultation. He suggested some useful resources. After work at the café, we talked about his favorite books!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2309&#34;&gt;23.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Got together with my group to work on a project. Discussed interesting problems. In the evening, there was a rush of customers at work, which only added to the adrenaline!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2409&#34;&gt;24.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today is a day off! Finally took a break from studying and working. Went to a museum exhibition, got inspired by new ideas. Back to the grind tomorrow!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Post from September 11 to 17</title>
      <link>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/post/summary2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/post/summary2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-happened-this-week&#34;&gt;What Happened This Week&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1609&#34;&gt;16.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today was the first quiz on Linear Algebra. I was a bit nervous, but I think I did okay. In the evening, back at work, but thoughts about the quiz keep lingering!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1709&#34;&gt;17.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spent the whole day at the library. So many books! Found some useful materials for preparing for the next quiz. Work at the café was calm, and I even managed to read a bit.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Post from September 1 to 3</title>
      <link>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/post/summary1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sergeantgarik.github.io/post/summary1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-happened-this-week&#34;&gt;What Happened This Week&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;0109&#34;&gt;01.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today was my first day at the university! So many new faces and impressions. I was a bit nervous during the Mathematical Analysis lecture, but the professor turned out to be very friendly. In the evening, I worked at the café and met some interesting people!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;0309&#34;&gt;03.09&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, my classmates and I decided to meet for coffee after classes. We discussed the upcoming exams and shared our study methods. I worked until late in the evening, but it didn’t stop me from feeling positive!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
